what UPS coppice a little bit of time
for people to get in here remember you
guys like the last mapping ones so I can
say what's up
yeah yeah I think you have to be careful
because I think if this loses the track
then it's not gonna work but as long as
we move it slowly and see the or
features over here yeah those are the
futures being streamed from the device
we're computing them on the Qualcomm DSP
y'all never never go to bed never sleep
are me did you sleep you know who
doesn't sleep now Ford sleeps man but we
don't sleep and that's why we're gonna
win so you can see them live streaming
the video over here so you guys can see
me holding the periscope with you that
is meta so you can see me I'm holding
you guys right you say yeah probably I
mean this is the same technology that's
in Apple's AR kit it's really very small
here we have an actual 3d map so this is
the same stuff that I was using to map
the roads except here it's a map of my
room so if I tilt it up you can see it
tilt up okay I'll make landscape sorry I
locked the rotation on my phone who
doesn't lock the rotation on that phone
yeah but so this technology is coming to
all your yawns very soon and then
combined with a great handle for the
places where our map does not have good
coverage this is going to give us ten
centimeters yeah new chair it's squeaky
I stole it I stole from someone else
yeah you want to come grease the chair
it's a little off it's terrible I'm
sorry guys sure it's terrible I check
out the comb pedal here's the comb
federal development station I'm very
upset with Eddie that he printed this
collar pedal in black because everybody
knows that comma pedals are light blue
a little LED blinking here tonight look
at that look so this is a common pedal
yeah I've been working on so that firmer
is pretty much done notice that we're
using all the Collard products this here
is a comedy bug
there's we're using it just exploded
giraffe you know what else we gonna use
I mean there's taken apart kama petal
good morning but ya know what's really
exciting is the mapping is the mapping
and uh yes here's oh I guess I need to
show you guys what was actually doing
the mapping here's an e on just sitting
on my desk again plugged into a comedy
bug yeah so now when I rotate this see
it map in real time over here yeah right
the mapping is exciting so I mean I
showed you guys in the last
late-night sundae mapping periscope
about how this actually works on the
roads
orab slim doesn't really work on a road
but if you combine it if you combine
these features let's see the features
over here if you combine the features
it's me and orb if you combine the
features with all the other stuff yeah
so what we found with the radar is the
problem with the radars is that they
have internal Kalman filters and if
we're putting that measurement into our
Calvin filter you can't double Kalman
filter like that unless we knew the
standard deviation from the raters which
we don't um obviously shame shame on
these radar people you know every time
like Tesla autopilot
accidents where it hits a stop car it's
really it's the radar like you can do a
much better job with this you know
radars killed a few people it's true
common radar I don't know so you want
you want to talk about um the visual
spectrum and why lidar is stupid I kind
of think actively emitting photons on
any spectrum is kind of stupid what do I
need to act the photons for look at what
I have working right and like this isn't
like this demo is not I built this demo
on a signal see for you guys this one
over on the left here I just piped the
frames into uh into a modified version
of orb slam but yeah you can see that
attracted this isn't using behind you or
anything we're working on the night is
scary well the night work at night as
well look it's me on the periscope
filming you it's like a triangle yeah
I've learned how to play chess you know
it's like yeah yeah just last night I
was reading about triangulating your
queen in the endgame triangulating yeah
it's gonna be functioning um dude like
honestly do we build things we don't
ship this is all gonna ship with with
the big gray Panda update and then we're
gonna start making precision maps and
we're gonna start real oka lysing you
and your precision maps so some of y'all
are gonna be part of the vakama commuter
Club the car needs to download what deta
yeah needs to download map data I'm
still be downloading map data from our
servers like I've said our maps are
gonna be open source the stuff is
starting to work really well if you're
an investor in a mapping company get out
now get out yeah wait no I point you
over there and I look over here get out
now
that's right don't be a mapping company
when can you join the community club
yeah I heard about the Iowa in the free
RTK I don't know sounds like I have to
yeah sure yes seriously I don't know man
I shorted mobile I once lost money I'm
over shorting anything on the stock
market
I only long clicked up which isn't doing
so long right now but don't worry crypto
will be back always long crypto but yeah
we can we can look I'm sitting here by
my by my three monitors like that to me
mom there's a pretty nice right oh yeah
we were going over we were going over
some companies
one of my slogans is convenience drives
success maybe there are the three kinds
of companies there's the uber - the
person company which is like way mo
cruising uber no mom the mom is not 4k
they're 1080 you don't really want for
came all of us let me do everything slow
so we stand a 4-man for your map data
I mean it's honestly just gonna be
coordinates in ecef ecef is Earth Center
earth fixed so these are these are
reimagining companies and then they make
cars better companies those are the two
companies honestly really aren't even
our competitors our competitors are just
just the status quo who wants to keep
cars the same or make cars worse you
know I've grown a new respect for mobile
over the years as I see we talked about
in the last test go
yeah that was that was the demo I have
prepared for you guys uh oh yeah if
you're with a mapping company get out I
mean here's why right so what a lot of
these mapping companies are doing is
they are spending a lot of money to
build one map and to try to maintain it
right so their overhead for mapping is
is very high our overhead for mapping is
actually negative we're providing value
to the users who map for us in the form
of open pilot right so you get open
pilot for free and we get data to make
maps I think that's a pretty good deal
and you also get that data obviously to
make your drives better you're going to
see immediate improvement once you start
mapping an area so if you are part of a
mapping company who is now spending
thousands maybe millions of dollars
compatible cars are on our github at
github.com slash comma AI slash open
pilot it's also I think it's linked from
our main site if you're at a mapping
company and you're trying to make a map
once if you're trying to spend a ton of
money on lidar cars and then you're
going to rent seek yeah yeah I SEOs I
SEOs are all on hold have you heard
about the new securities laws you guys
been seeing that the New York Times and
stuff you know I like that idea
you guys know I like that idea but um no
I mean look what we're clearly providing
value to the users right not only to get
not only get the dash cam to get shiver
but like open pilot Oh pile it's a
pretty good deal um we're not gonna map
your garage we're gonna try to only map
things that we deem are on a roads I
don't want a map in your garage I don't
want to know
contrarily Metroid's VA knows that
they're gonna be on our on our open
source map and it's going to be
contributed to and healed by all of our
cars just driving a cross at all right
and in like pokeymon mapping I mean
here's the thing right this is a Ark it
but for the world so
if you think about it like that right
you think about a are kitten a our kid
can like do my one room this is a our
kit for the world you want to put a real
like who stole what's though who stole
the a are cute guys actually doing
something similar doing whose company
called Napper AI I'm all the Erica
people left Apple they were startup
anyway who basically built that stuff is
that a heatmap originated from my pandas
car kid yeah mapper a I um so that's a
better idea I mean you have like mapper
today I and your little five Traver
I mean you know it just they
misunderstand what the hard problem is
[Music]
yeah so we're gonna start building we're
gonna start building this map out you're
gonna be able to get to it at a map Maps
dot comma dot ai once it's done is there
Pokemon or no should we put Pokemon on
our map I mean it's yeah we think we can
aar the world right I mean why don't we
sell the advertising in the AR right toy
sell advertising is that the kind of
person I am
what am I gonna give more details on
comic commuters so maps are first first
we're gonna launch the very early beta
of comma map I mean everybody who has a
gray Panda and neon will be able to
contribute to the common map if you have
two gray pandas your stuff will show up
on the map instantly if you have only
one gray panda it will take longer um
and that's because we need to wait for
for data to download from the UH from
the US government and we know that
they're not very fast which car did he
get and he got his own car I don't know
what car you got I think we might go buy
a Ford Fusion tomorrow you guys know I
was talking about that earlier on the
slack but yeah so um if you if you are
friends with someone in a mapping
company you know tell them the
apocalypse is coming if if if you how
will I make you rich buy buy a Ford
Fusion
I'll make me poor around I'll give money
to Ford I don't feel great about that
but you know hey everyone else is using
Ford fusions and you know what they say
most of the time when everyone else is
doing
something by a semi I'm not doing
Sammy's common team is 12 people
apologies what ghosts driving yeah yeah
fusion yeah no it turbo all those s got
turbo
I got a turbo in my Ford Fusion what the
finance was a great man we're killing it
shop down calm down oh yeah are we
shield for the merch oh we show for the
merchants hoodie you can't even get bro
you can't even get this if you've
got a hoodie you got in early um ml guys
still there well you know ml is ml ml is
a tough tough tough field guys still
here yeah but you know don't expect new
models I know some of your L expect the
new models um you know when we come out
with a new model you're gonna look at it
and you're gonna be like holy
that's like a year ahead of anything
Tesla's on autopilot we're gonna crush
him are we gonna crush him because we're
finally doing away with the original
Senate comma a I which is lanes lanes
are very bad and we don't have lanes in
our new model under model won't have
lanes our new model will just be like go
there and go there is exactly what you
want from model sandbagging the new
models are gonna be great but the new
models are still a long ways away so yes
the ml team is still here but you know
ml takes a long time aha so there's
there's that we have a bunch of things
to do before the new models and we don't
really talk about our ml strategy
because it is secret but you know it's
not secret our mapping strategy our
mapping strategy is 100% public for open
source maps and it basically looks like
this
we're running a super modified version
let's not even orb slam anymore on the
back end we're just running gto which is
the optimizer orb slam uses to build
maps then once we have maps will stream
them back to our devices so you can
localize in them and then once we have
maps well when you have a map see that's
the real way to do more torque safely
right you don't you don't want swerving
when you're on a highway oh but if you
know places where you can
need torque you can limit the torque
based on where you are in the map and
this is a great safe way to roll out
higher torques so we can we can talk
about that if you don't have a platform
ie Tesla car itself Tech's less sticks
its customers with its own property you
will launch on what car brow have you
followed Khamenei I do you have a Honda
or Toyota go right now to come at AI
github back on slash comedy I slash open
pilot and you'll find that there's
actually some free software out there
that can drive your Honda's and Toyota
so what car are we gonna launch on the
Honda's and the Toyotas and maybe also
of the tasarov I see some great progress
with that GM port we'd love to see it
upstream get you paid out that money you
know we're thinking about buying a Ford
tomorrow that's gonna be Honda Tesla GM
Ford lexus lexus is already supported we
already support the lexus RS that's
right acura Honda's are just Acuras
Toyota's are just lexus lexus they're
just Toyota's Acuras just Honda anymore
car hacking going on right now we are
always doing car hacking you guys want
to see a pre CC you I'll show you guys a
Prius steering controller what pothole
detection well yeah who likes potholes
man no not infinity check it out they're
really cute actually he this is the ECU
the Toyota uses for all the steering um
so what you'll find if you look at this
is the guy over here is where the power
comes in this one here is where the
motor goes out and notice how many wires
it has it has two so it looks like
Toyota's using like just a brushed motor
um which is a little sketchy
I mean the reason to brush motor is a
little sketchy is because if you have
that latch up that's kind of a playful
torque to the motor which isn't great
especially also this thing oh it does
have a relay okay alright so it does
have a lockout relay here you can see
this relay I think that that is locking
out the fats to prevent that latch up so
that's a good thing
um so there's a bit of safety in here
which is good but you know brushless
motors are inherently more safe than
brushed motors because if you get fetch
feta you don't you get like weird
behavior but you're not going to get you
know slamming the steering wheel to the
left or to the right so then you see
right here this port is where you plug
in the torque sensor and this port here
is where you plug in the power and the
can and these are the little cute Toyota
steering controllers that look like
they're in most of the new Toyota so
it's nice I don't know what chips
actually in here this one looks like a
FET driver this one is the
microcontroller running the code so the
Prius has parking assist I don't know
why this is only in the Prius I don't
know why this isn't in the other cars
I'm so the Prius you can actually put a
lot of torque on the steering wheel it's
enough torque to do South Park but I
don't think it's the steering column
that's different but the Prius does have
other weird qualities so maybe there are
some differences in the steering column
I didn't build this house I didn't hang
the chandeliers
I do like another kind of nice right
yeah Prius ECU
here's another Prius CCO this is a
hybrid controller Prius ECU this is the
one that I bricked well this isn't the
one that I bricked this is the spare now
in case I break it again but I own brick
tit so it's all good yeah the ref will
just have ultrasonic it doesn't have
active Park Assist it can't like spin
the wheel
am I still into iDevice hacking I
couldn't care less
i device hacking had its time back when
phones were bad in 2007 phones were bad
you needed to hack them 2008 phones were
bad you needed to hack them you know
with bad in 2018 cars that's why we had
cars gotta make cars good how did i
brick it
I did I forgot it I missed a checksum
all the Toyota code when you add it all
together needs to add to a a 5/5 I don't
believe in passions I think that that's
a stupid way to look at it people are
always like find your passion in life
that is stupid advice um just do
whatever the hell you want alright
work is the only thing I've ever really
found satisfying I mean what else is
satisfying sitting around spoke a weed I
like smoking weed but you know what you
can smoke weed and work that's great
janna works the only thing I've ever
found really satisfying in a long time
so yeah I did this this is what I do
women weed and working
how about Nissan's any port guy smock
ass Oh check out my Omaha
check out my omaha sweatpants brevin
gave these to me when i visited omaha um
smock ass i don't know what that
means smock ass i like yeah check out
the quality sign that's too much you see
you know no I don't really cook the
works don't know I just I just made a
mistake
am i high now no what did i do today I
had I had I had a mate' oh and I have
one of these these things really do get
me wired though no I'm not high we could
have this much energy if I was hide
these things man I did have one of these
today they kind of do get me wired I do
have more respect for mobilize yeah
mobilize not as bad um yo maybe we'll go
smoke weed after this maybe maybe after
the scope he goes away well uh smoke we
don't play some chess right that sounds
like something to do um yeah I do it
more respect from oh boy you know I
still don't really have respect for
sorry guys
this is our Zuke's poster this is why we
don't build cars yeah sorry zukes I
don't believe in his future this is a
big house you live alone right now yeah
I'm the only one living here oh this is
the office right like this isn't this is
my house this is the company I office
yes a nice poster right check out these
there's this one this this is made by a
micro intern check out our h-1b
application forms it's really hard to
give visas for people what now I'm never
gonna say superglue bro
but yeah so for those who aren't here at
the beginning of the periscope looks
like we got a few more people
check out the mapping set up so this is
just our I have an e on here on my desk
that I'm using and now that crashed yeah
it's not I like it's not really orb slam
it
doesn't real oka lies because what do
you need to realize for when you have
GPS what are our micro interns doing we
have two micro interns coming this week
one is interviewing for the
infrastructure position and one is
interviewing for the JavaScript position
to work on Cabana and shiver we have two
interns coming this summer which we're
very excited about
we have a great Android hacker coming in
to improve stability and quality of knee
OS really get neo s open sourced and we
have a phenomenal ml intern I got this
guy on the phone and he just you know he
knew yeah he had similar ideas on how to
actually solve this problem no we don't
do remote work only in very rare
circumstances on machine learning
interns yet we have a phenomenal machine
learning intern coming this summer I'm
very excited
interns sleep in the basement no you
guys want to see what I could take you
at an intern sleep we do have we do have
intern housing would you offer intern
housing a comment I of course right
because I always wish that like like
other things offered intern housing what
kind of company do I run we r comma AI
and we're gonna win self-driving cars
that's what kind of company we run a
winning company that's right no but like
seriously you guys see what we're doing
we're very open what kind of questions
do I ask for ml during the interview
well you got it you got an interview to
find out if I tell you my questions and
other people will watch the periscope
and then all of the answers and then it
won't be a good test you can make good
lemonade listen to gucci mane song
lemonade that's what i have to say to
that how do you apply give me a job at
Khamenei I um take more money from VCS
and hire faster we have a lot of money
our problems not money um the problem so
like there's this myth and this is one
of my contrarian positions that more
people solve a problem faster I don't
necessarily think that that's true yeah
we can help you with visas we would
definitely help with visas I don't
necessarily think that like just
throwing more people at a problem will
solve
faster I think that if you want to
problem-solve faster it's really
important how you set up like management
structures and the way that people work
together because management and I'll say
the word collaboration is really really
hard alright let's go up to enter in
housing I'll show you guys in turn
housing scobie's yeah no it is about
quality it's really all about quality we
hire honestly with the average IQ income
AI as it's got to be insane
so alright alright alright we're going
into housing
welcome to intern housing so we have a
bunk bed here so we can fit two interns
I'm gonna sit down on the intern bed
here a little desk for interns to do
work at that light doesn't work let's go
plug the wagon oh there's no plug
oh there it is there we go alright
scobie's hope that was fun to join me
yeah right is this intern housing umm
you live right where your work so you
commute it's pretty good I mean it's a
few room in San Francisco guys what am i
doing these days
car hacking I've been on the car hacking
team this week we are gonna do a pop-up
shop I'm really excited about the pop-up
shop but don't tell the regulators cuz
we're just showing up man I don't mean
like the regulator's like dish to end
stuff we're cool with them now I mean
the regulator's like whoever regulates
pop-up shops because I heard that Logan
Paul who am NOT a fan of anymore
Logan Paul that's too harsh - Logan Paul
I think Logan Paul will get his act back
together but I have a fan of pewdiepies
to go out there and watch our PewDiePie
Oh dev kits right yeah no no we sell
deaf kids no it's not that it's just
like I'm sure you need like a permit to
set up a pop-up shop and you know me I'm
gonna show up on a corner with like cart
maybe we'll like open the back of the
rav4
automatically and we will you know just
start selling alright where do I see
coming in five years I think we're gonna
win self-driving cars um
I mean okay look guys look obviously you
can look at me and it could be like well
I'm delusional right like how could how
could we possibly win you know we have I
say we have a lot of money we do have a
lot of money but not compared to you
know these people have poured like
billions into it but I don't think that
matters I think what matters in the
future is like avoiding regressions and
shipping if you manage to build and you
manage to ship something a little bit
better and a little bit better and a
little bit better yeah Pass Elon is
looking easier and easier
where is he launch cross-country Drive I
thought that's where he would be by now
right I thought that that was gonna get
done I'm a little bit surprised that
hasn't been like I say I'm nice
delusional than I were two years ago
that's probably true I'm surprised it
hasn't been done so yeah I mean if e1
doesn't like this year is still ahead
but by the end of this year I think we
will be able to do that cross-country
Drive are we doing stock options to
employees absolutely absolutely if
you're trying to start up early stage of
course stock options good eventually -
um no it's not that success no community
right like the community is a great
asset I do love you guys I love a comma
are me proud to be a member of the comma
army um the community the community is
great and like what it gives us is is
feedback um if we're shipping
you guys will tell us right if Zook
spends their days doing who
tells them right so by actually shipping
and by closing that feedback loop it
gives us a really cool advantage that I
mean who else has that advantage like
Tesla alright now I can talk about where
Tesla stopped and why there haven't been
autopilot updates lately I think what
Tesla's done over the last year is built
something that we've been building from
day one and that's really good
infrastructure to gather all the videos
from the car
because you know Tesla just didn't
really have the kind of training data
they needed yeah yeah I feel good about
the current sensor suite it's not just a
single camera we have another sensor
that we've shipped obviously you guys
know what it is who knows what the other
sensor is the sensor I promised it for a
while I will do that self-driving
awareness to again next year and we'll
have less disengagement that's I think
that like that stuff's kind of gimmicky
too like rice it for one GPS exactly um
so we shipped the gray panda which is
another sensor in conjunction with the
open-source comma AI map yeah so you're
gonna get that great sensor as well if
you haven't if you have great panda and
an internet connection you get a second
sensor after the single camera no
there's obviously some stuff you can't
do with a single camera and we know that
but we do still feel good about it till
the end of the year there's a whole lot
of the problem to solve on a single
camera and you guys know we're cellphone
company right first year the absolute
first year of karma I we built the comma
zero I showed it to Bloomberg the second
year we built the comma neo then we
called it the well we built two comma
one and we called it the Neo when we
shipped last year we built the comma E
on so next year we'll build the comma
three right yes we're cell phone company
we're looking to ship new hardware every
year just like any cell phone company
will continue hopefully to support the
old hardware for one year after that but
no real promises on that but we'll try
our best on the you know it's quite a
good platform there's a lot of stuff
that's still unused on that so like I
said that thing that I showed you the
vision thing was running on the DSP
which is another completely unused part
of the chip in your D on the depth map
using camera are working on that no no
no no the commentaries nothing fun but
we are like a phone company we're going
to ship new hardware every year
why no love to BMW because it uses flex
write anything that uses Flex ray is
difficult no not a different smartphone
no I think I think that this is going to
be the last smartphone , product though
the EON will be said
ordered for quite a long time I mean of
course there's gonna be an update you
know I'm not gonna ever lie and say you
know that's it that's it
the Aeons gonna solve software in cars
it's not right you need more hardware
than that obviously but I think by the
end of the year and maybe with a demo
that we have coming up in a few months
you're gonna be like wait did you really
put that in the yawn yeah we put in the
EON right um no cross country is cross
country is it who cares I care about
people's commutes I care about making
people's computes have less
disengagement making people's can be
what's nicer do I think new cars will
ship with some extra security people ask
me that question a lot I always say
Apple couldn't stop me and Sony couldn't
stop me what hope to Honda and Toyota
have when are we gonna run out of 1+3
never never never never never actually
no I shouldn't say that
what do I'll show you guys this document
we have stacks and stacks and stacks of
eons I should get a stock room we have a
lot right now but yeah we'll probably
run out middle of this year so we'll
have to figure out how to get more yeah
we're gonna develop our own hardware
platform ah because I mean we have the
EON is a hardware platform all right oh
we put a phone inside of it yeah we put
phone inside we're who cares what was
the other question there's another
question I forget what it was
can you make self-driving bikes no that
means you want it to pedal you want
electric bike you want to steer for you
you want the balance for you you know
who did that though
Anthony Levin to ask you right hype for
auger yeah of course I'm alive trogir
man I think my reps gonna fall in price
but I'm still hyped for it
um Snapdragon Hardware no probably not
you know who will use it do you think
ways actually makes people more stressed
I don't think so I think it makes it
less stress
thank you virtually Chris thank you good
to see you again yeah no we just went
over we just went over mapping and yeah
we talked some about some companies
not really I think I choose a pretty
positive periscope trying to be more
positive positivity you guys
I love positivity this is a nice fruit
when interns move out I'll probably move
in here and then my rooms in this house
too and
can move out and put more people in
there tensorflow on-device we do that
already
what do you think that model was trained
with the one that shipped envisioned a
stencil off I can't even guys I'm trying
to be positive on this periscope I get
even room to her no no no this is the
only room you guys get to see today what
did I love prior to mapping we love
mapping and mapping the big thing this
year I'm the one from the GPUs man is
Kama HQ moving to LA now I like to talk
about that right you guys know team ten
you know Jake Paul's thing we're gonna
be team eleven we're gonna be twice as
lit team eleven it's logarithmic deal
eleven TV 11 bro no comma army for life
make sure to hit that like and subscribe
button it's no like bought on periscope
if you can hit that make sure to smash
that like a subscribe button
move to the east coast now that moment I
love these coasts but here's what they
say about your company your company's
valuation is 5x higher in San Francisco
yeah we're mapping bro what happened
take the survey will you start sending
the e on with the 1 + 5 now nope yawns
we'll all be one plus three T's and yeah
that's what yawns will be you do a lot
with that phone
um when moon guys so how many eyes
growth has been um well you know what
they say about exponential it looks
linear at the beginning but I think that
these nuts right I've voted for Deez
Nuts I tried to but you know I just out
of the race yeah 2016 Deez Nuts no but I
think I think the virality of commenting
eyes a little bit different from the
virality of okay alright come on man
what kind of a name is that invited Bob
black I love blocking people am i dating
uh no
No you know you just got a dating like I
don't even know what that means anymore
man
like dating really confusing what you
gotta like I don't know I don't know
what it means in the modern to know in
the modern tinder era
what does dating mean right that's
something to think about like it's not
well we're gonna get married and have
kids and move in together I don't know
am i okay
yeah I'm okay I'm good I'm good I trip
to Thailand I went to Thailand I found I
went to some of those places this is
kind of a little shady right like you
see like the kind of guys you show up at
those things I'm way the name comma come
from so if you want to have a successful
company it's got to be two syllables and
it's got to be between four and nine
letters did I meet ladyboys there are
yeah you see some lady voice that is
real Thailand stuff who hurt you don't
cry do I look sad what's sad super-shady
you gonna tweet when pop-up shop happens
uh yeah we'll tweet when the pop-up shot
happens
what does dating me guys you guys got
you guys got me psyched out man Oh name
was coming from um nobody understand
what I'm saying right like it's oh I
found one gray panda I found one gray
Panda when I was cleaning the basement
we of course will periscope the pop-up
shop uh no like there was this storm and
when I showed you guys this door and I
thought about I thought about going
there papa
periscope oh yeah no I did that's the
last girl I dated I did I did I dated a
girl uh two years ago before before the
company no it's it's I'm not sure if the
world's changing her arm changing see
that's something you always have to
think about who's changing is you or is
it the world
you don't know cuz there's only one
world there's only one you these are the
things I think about
the world I mean the world is changing
right but you see that's the thing like
can you really know that I think we're
both changing right there's a there's a
real friends you know you're good thing
you abandon I know this place is the
same and I'm just changing right and
it's about going back to like your you
know your suburban home that you grew up
in and you know the place is the same
and you've changed is the bounty
mechanism for supporting more cars a
long-term plan bounty is one of the
strategies using the Deep Web no he's to
do drugs I don't really do drugs that
much anymore so what am i buying on the
Deep Web
I smoke weed you know Slee Galia the
California uh y know South by this year
they didn't invite me to speak um I
probably would have went it's kind of
fun to use a thing right the first year
I gave this and you can see The Verge
article about it the first year I gave
this speech where it's like I'm gonna
hand capitalism who thought leadership
right and then the second year I'm like
okay wait number like this is actually
what we're doing um you smoke weed and
are able to code and run a startup I
don't smoke I don't like wake up in the
morning and I'm like smoke weed right um
why don't you use eye glasses why do I
need eyeglasses have perfect vision Bros
anymore car hacking tools for the
community coming out cabanas gonna get
improved what phone am i using you guys
know what phone I'm using what phone am
i using those very much check is pretty
sexy right um no in trucking in trucking
way most strategy makes sense I don't
actually use tinder tinder is a terrible
terrible dating app
shipper is ship is a better app to news
it's tackle um let's play there's plenty
of women if you know where to lock you
know but they so got yelled at me for
not being politically correct on my
periscopes last time he sent me a
message on twitter is like be
politically correct bro and here's what
I said back to him like if we live in a
world where people are too afraid to
speak their mind then I don't know what
kind of world we live in but that's not
an excuse to be a sexist or racist don't
do that that's that's bad beautify
I think we talked before crying I'm not
gay sometimes I wish I wasn't be pretty
cool I think being gay in San Francisco
be a pretty cool experience um this is
this is personally guests a real
personal periscope telling you deep
thoughts you know it's more personal
than like Apple or Amazon Amazon Amazon
because Apple has already dominated
their markets Amazon actually still has
a lot more to grow I have investors in
both though I do believe that both will
grow but I do think Amazon will beat
Apple to be the next trillion dollar
company um I also think that Apple is I
mean look are they trillion topples not
trillion um Tim Cook is great at running
things and that's the kind of person he
is but like will Apple be the leader in
the next thing I don't know I kind of
don't see it whereas Amazon you know you
still have Bezos they're right jobs Ian
Apple would be an Amazon any day cookie
and Apple maybe not we did use AWS until
we ran out of the free money and now we
use our free money on Azure I'm not
touching anything Sony you know guys
have a permanent injunction and allowed
to hack any Sony products um I couldn't
care less about the Sony products either
what I sell to Jeff here's the thing
about selling right if I thought some
company could help us could being bought
by that company could help us achieve
kamas mission faster which is winning
self-driving cars then I would be good
with that um but I mean you gotta you
got a win right okay I won't tell anyone
you're good bro um test your software
hardware outside the USA we ship
worldwide bro we don't test we ship we
simply test a little bit we test them in
the basement of the testing closet can
we trade in a white pen of a cheaper
gray pen and a bro cave Jeep oh my god
integrating with a large clubs better
than selling for a chunk of change yeah
maybe
what's winning for comma I mean wouldn't
it be nice if we could sell a box that
you put no those refunds within 30 days
if you don't like the product if you
just want next year's product I mean you
can't like buy the iPhone 7 and then the
iPhone
comes out you're like Apple could I
trade in my iphone 7iphone is not a good
example I think that's actually true am
i a good programmer I mean you can read
my code I'll go my github github.com
such geo hot um I guess I don't know be
doing that recent up there Kiera's
probably the last big thing I wrote so
you can read my code and you can judge
for yourself whether you think of a good
program or not okay better hacker than
programmer
yeah I do I submit connect I bought the
dip I bought the dip
I thought big connect might rebound and
I lost that eat so let's just say that's
one you don't never see again
oh my Amazon Prime now order will arrive
soon sweet about some hard drives her
computer we had a micro intern coming
tonight don't get to get him a computer
uh Toyota firmware hack soon TM yeah PCI
max soon
why pandas so expensive panda not
expected a pen a not expensive only $99
cheap umm what language do i code in
Python mostly um I'm pretty good at C as
well no I bought SSDs of course I want
access to is what is the hard drives
these it's just an SSD I'm pretty good
at sea
I can read C++ you asked me to code
anything and C++ I'm a lot worse at it I
realize I don't know any modern
JavaScript anymore um you know I know
like jQuery or JavaScript
so that's true I spent like two weeks
learning rust um yeah I built some
things takes a long time uh I made this
one thing in go and realized absolutely
hated go I like rust I like the idea of
rust just winning mean always staying
open source and not staying to a single
car company winning means shipping um I
don't really open source is nice I think
open source has a lot of strategic
advantages that are really
underappreciated how old am I'm 28 if
pandas expensive comply dad's a lidar
Java programmer program I have a wait
like do people not like think I'm a
programmer I mean obviously I'm a
programmer right
UI mods it doesn't really work that well
uh-oh yeah you can bet it knob you can
buy a knockoff you can buy a cheap China
oh btw dunno then like try to use it for
like driving your car and I like won't
work bro like this fine I don't know
like you got to ask yourself do you buy
nice things if you buy cheap knockoff
things you can buy cheap knockoff things
don't work well some cheap knockoff
things are good to buy it when someone
makes an actually good knockoff panda
for $30 tell everybody to buy it no
that's the thing like what do you think
I am some kind of like business CEO I
could certainly code
am I like a great like programmer like
Jeff Dean I don't think so uh neither
publishing papers is kind of overrated
what I consider common level three by
December probably not I think level
three is more like a year and a half
away um to actually be level three I
think that we need I mean okay I think
you get the kind of reliability you need
for level three you're gonna need both a
really good ml model and you're gonna
need maps and with those two combined I
think you can get to level three does
open pilot work well in Europe try it
yeah I think so
not not know they drivin left Germany
right now I kind of work see today I'm
gonna left - I think Carmack is better
than Dean maybe a cart Carmack Carmack's
a good programmer as well yeah he's you
know he wrote fine he's kind of doing
small like stuff to us you know writing
there I think if you are can yawn get to
level three probably not maybe depending
on the car lane change part of level
three it doesn't have to be I'm so level
three basically just means looking for
the best programmers guys I think I have
a set of skills I think are very good
systems thinker like it is Elon Musk a
good programmer
I don't know coming not that good um I
think I could probably go better than
him but you know it's not like
programming is a it's it's a it's a
almost a rote skill to some point like
systems architecting is where it's
really at but if you can't like prove
yourself programming which I think Ilan
did and I think I did when I was younger
if you want to see if you want to see
some good code of mine I wrote this I
wrote this exploit I wrote a the
Chromebook exploit and Google made it
open source you can find like geo hot
zip and he can read an exploit of mine
and it's it's quite well liked commented
and document it and stuff like I'm
handing this code
you know I want to impress it right
that's what I kind of still respected
Google it's sad we're good to go
but that's that's a topic for another
day that's definitely topic for another
day it is sad that Google uh I think
they've lost away Chromebook Expo yeah
just come back x-play I want $150,000
for it
back in the day back in uh 2014 I don't
talk about my past much can you use it
for open Network attacks knowledge I
handed it to Google I I responsible
disclosed it right not that I think
responsible disclosure matters but um I
will responsibly disclose an exploit if
you'll pay me $150,000 now I haven't
done a CTF in a while and this CTF says
good at them no I didn't reserve a model
three
I don't think Tesla wants people buying
their cars what do I do now
you said an intern housing in periscope
what about Google would that Laffy
Taffy's I wish I could scroll back in
the chat I can't
yo guys you want to hear something
that's actually like shitty Mars Chris I
got seven years in jail like that's not
even like a joke because super shitty
for for not losing anybody any money
like I I don't want a billion dollars I
think we talked about that last time I
don't know what I would do with a lot of
money I don't really want money I don't
care I want to build better stuff are
you
ADHD what does that mean why did I leave
project zero um
project zero I was an intern there I
don't want to do that as a full-time
career free scrolly I agree I agree I
you know I was with some people we
protested outside the Twitter building
when he got banned from Twitter uh have
I drank alcohol
not tonight have I drank alcohol with my
life yes um you could go skiing every
day with the billion dollars yeah you
guys don't understand like I'm already
rich I go skiing every day already it's
not what I want to do with my life um
are you OCD I don't know what these
things mean bro I did go to CMU and my
OCD and my ADHD you mean some like quack
who went to like like that darah you
know school
they studied how to like when the
marketing reps come and offer you a free
trip to Hawaii for marketing wa tughda
say yes
that's what they learn in med school
baby I don't know yeah chance again
weird net worth I never very low
maintenance leak on the floor it's just
not that kind of stuff doesn't matter to
me
I'm comfortable enough that I could live
off the interest of what I have are you
soap my son of a bitch no don't dairy
dare insult my mother like that
um battery died I think my battery's
alive everyone's keen on figures huh you
know I was younger
ah what neural thing yeah I've been here
two years and we got three more now
let's go you guys being rich is a scam
I've always felt that you know actually
if you haven't seen check out my raps
soundcloud.com slapped Tom Cruise that's
Tom Cruise with two zeros inspired by
James Dean with two E's damn I'm feeling
okay it's really getting late I'm
shilling for my rap account we saw 66
people will go to an hour in here what
are my thoughts about Facebook's
platform Facebook's a media company but
actually I have seen some sort of like
self awareness this year which I like
from Facebook and from Mark Zuckerberg I
don't know I mean maybe he doesn't know
what it means to make the world more
open and connected and he really is
trying yeah the Kolar more track is
pretty good I did put a lot of effort
into that new tracks oh man I did oh all
right all right all right all right you
want to go get my laptop I'll do a rap
track I got this is this is something
most I was I was writing right because
of those work enough I'm not gonna
release it on a on soundcloud so I
figure I can just get my laptop and
perform a few guys you know like the
quavo style rap yeah if you care about
self-driving cars this is nothing to do
with self-driving cars this is this is
just getting late
it is late though I'm waiting for my
Amazon Prime look it's still running how
stable so stable all right chop it up no
one lets the other rap track although I
got here no no it's not it's not
self-driving
[Applause]
what Amazon Prime package yeah I'm his
longtime delivers late we love Amazon
Prime all right I have it I have like I
have this song according to Roger no
we're really gonna do the rap I don't
think we're really gonna do the rap
should we really do the rap here's the
beat I got if it doesn't come I'm going
to be very upset with Amazon look we got
like a quavo be right
that I his we got yo I just I download
these beats off the internet and I'm a
terrible I'm like a YouTube rapper II
know this is not where my talents lie
we're gonna put in video in every car
maybe I'm flipping a gremlin - spatula
down in Atlanta with Georgia's the
Capitol I made a pinky from my pan and
I'll bring back a spatula poured and
flap it up
time to go merry-go-round people don't
marry the ground the dirt is so this
isn't sleeping around I hear this
because people will sleep with you now
Seraphim brother don't wrap it up look
what I'm making to stack it up you can
all watch it go put some ice cream on
that bitch and some fruit like bananas
and outta there got a few jets in my
haters back to the kitchen in the break
you know I got so much money wondering
what they will say now I find them and
ask if they want a pancake and they eat
but they all look so big now know which
is good but they gotta admit that y'all
can see just be getting paid now looks
like I got the way now you can tuck it
with a pole now y'all be my pancake I'm
the king of the playground
alright that's very shkreli ish play
with that like quavo right I can't
want to go sit in the room boy yeah
thanks thanks Bros I'm sorry me alright
alright I think on that note we will
leave it now I gotta finish the track
right maybe maybe I'll finish the track
I have a lot of Blake unwritten wraps
that are kind of like crappy only wait
you see on Tom Cruise's Ali scrappy
which is really not saying much man I
wanna be a rapper when I grow up but you
know what I got better things to do you
know what you know I realized today and
we'll leave it on this note the sky's
funny man no but here's what we're gonna
leave off with today but I'm not a
rapper alright um know what we gonna
leave off with today is guys I'm down to
do this you know for the last like last
year I was always like okay
how do you put the board away right you
play the game of chess you know it's
great about chess whether you win or
lose you put the board away board goes
away you shake hands good game we can
all appreciate a chess a little bit more
right but companies don't end that way
companies either last forever or die and
it sucks it sucks and but you know what
like if I want to live forever then why
shouldn't I make the company last
forever this is this is this is what I
want to do and this is um I wanna look
forever I gotta make the company last
forever I don't know guys like uh when's
the next big product release it's all
coming in time right we're a lot like a
cell phone company we're gonna come out
with new hardware every year
um just print two organs I mean no it's
just about it's about the future I want
to live in right and I think that
there's way too much just so much
negativity in the world that I really
and I'm just not I don't feel negative
anymore I think that we can build a
great world I think that things are
really exciting I think that crypto is
really exciting I think that
self-driving cars are really exciting I
think that AI is really exciting I think
that these things are gonna I'm not
gonna say like like people talk about
people talk about like empathy and stuff
and then you read like there's a book
like again so much has it oh my oh my
friends been delivered whoa yo let's go
get it boys oh I love packages man you
know that's what they say never never
grow up and never stop being excited
when your packages arrive let's go let's
go see what I got yeah boy look at that
look at that oh by the way I don't think
you guys can really see it but it's
beautiful out here
I don't think you can see it all but
it's really beautiful
um packages like Christmas presents
exactly right when you're an adult
Christmas is all about like that person
from the family's coming right but
that's Christmas I got to see people I
got to interact I got to be polite
Wow Christmas I love my family guess you
got a lovely folder
let's see what I got okay right here
this isn't that exciting I have a three
pack of HDMI cables I got him a brand
new hard drive Samsung SSD 580 Evo it
was on sale and I also got us every
system Amazon does trihard I also got
another ebo you see this whole area
we're throwing these couches away we're
gonna we're gonna put some desks there
this is H not hard drive it is an SSD
it's SS these are hard drives but what
is it okay it's hard man like it's hard
hard drive PC but I don't guys honestly
I play Age of Empires Super Smash
Brothers 64 and Jess these are the games
I play I'm old I'm old but no I'm the
note we were gonna leave it on is you
guys we're on an amazing journey where
they are and I don't know I mean they
always say look for me yeah smash of the
night play I go 64 I got a second floor
I got a CRT TV it's never that good at
Starcraft I was good when it first came
out and then everybody like just
memorized build order isn't like I don't
play this game anymore
yeah that's it's exciting and from an
outside perspective you look and you're
like okay I mean look I got a seer I
like like like how can uh how can you
win right how can how can how can calm a
win but then again from the outside
perspective like who's shipping nobody
we're you know I drove I drove autopilot
ooh and a model 3 I mean it's some parts
it's better than open pilots some parts
it's worse it's a matter of taste
how is that possible I tried out GM
supercruise it's good one common isn't
one yet it's good when it works but did
you know it just drops out a lot of
times and you don't really know why it's
just like sorry I can't engage here I
have no idea why I write like open pilot
kind of gracefully degrades supercruise
is like you got a drive bro Google's
gonna ship lidar sensors I think one of
the greatest things in the world
okay we're definitely not going past an
hour with this I think one of the
greatest things in the world it's like a
problem is kind of like like maybe the
word I use is virtue signaling why lidar
right like like the people who are
always so pro lighter can you really
articulate why it's better than cameras
Oh super cruise does monitor your eyes
ah visiting random chat was go be some
day no agenda we always have agendas but
then they devolve into this they devolve
into sitting on the couch I'm sure
talking about I trying to be positive
trying to be positive cut positive
because positivity big fish all right
we'll leave it at that
all right a little bit that if you're
investing in a lighter company what if
the dirt on your lidar if you're
investing in a lighter company or you're
investing in a mapping company get out
if you're investing in comma a I you're
gonna be rich
no promises that's not a stock holder
promise or something
he said you uh five hundred II mean I'm
not gonna keep you FAC underneath bro
but yeah all right thanks for joining
later scobie's